Good evening everyone, I am Xuanli from the Chinese team of Icy Marvelous Design.
In today's live course, we will learn how to make this set of jeans.
A few days ago, we started the 5th edition of the 3D props competition with Lurtis Studio.
The registration period for this episode is until September 5th.
If you are interested, you can watch our previous videos to sign up.
The theme of this episode is Western Salon.
I have prepared a live course about how to make this set of jeans.
I hope it can help you.
Let's get started.
Let's take a look at the overall effect of this set of clothes.
It has a jacket, a triangle, a shirt, jeans, etc.
In today's video,
I will show you how to make this set of jeans.
It will take a long time.
So you can prepare a small plate of snacks to watch this video.
This video will have a live broadcast.
The follow-up live broadcast will be uploaded to the official account of Marvelous Designer, MD official.
Now let's get started.
First of all, you can see that I made this set of clothes.
I made this set of clothes with a basic model.
The body shape of this model is a little stronger.
So if we import this set of T-shirt files from Marvelous Designer,
you will see that it will pass through the human body.
Because the size of this human body is a little bigger than the male body shape of this set of clothes.
This model file will be uploaded in the later part of today's live broadcast.
Then it will be uploaded together.
So if you want to learn with this,
you can click on the comment section below the video.
As you can see,
because our body shape is a little bigger than the T-shirt body shape of the original T-shirt,
we need to re-arrange the board.
To prevent the board from interfering with the model during the arrangement process.
Because there is an interference,
sometimes it cannot return to the correct place of wearing by itself.
So we need to re-arrange the board.
When arranging the board,
there is a tab in the right side of the selectable board.
Adjusting this tab can keep the board away from the body of the virtual model.
After the adjustment is complete,
we will start to adjust the board.
Because when we make clothes in the software,
the first thing to modify is its overall shape,
and then we need to increase it.
And then we need to add some other details.
So when we are making the most internal layer of this shirt,
first of all, we know that this set of clothes,
its size is not compatible with this model.
So we can open the hard drive.
Just now we will see that the hard drive will see the model.
It has some pressure on the top.
That is, the pressure is relatively large.
Since this is the case,
we need to adjust the board
to fit the body shape of the virtual model.
Before we adjust the board,
because this set of clothes is a relatively tight dress,
all of our models have an air thickness around them,
which is the surface diameter.
And when our board has a larger particle diameter,
when wearing tight clothes,
it is difficult to see some of its fold effect.
Because the particle diameter is larger,
the size of the board is relatively small,
so the fold effect is not detailed enough.
So for this dress,
I have already reduced its particle diameter in the previous period,
and the thickness of the board has been reduced.
This is also to make it easier to see the fold effect.
In the process of moving the board,
you will see that when I move the board,
because the board is too tight,
the fold effect is not very beautiful.
And this fold effect is not the fold effect I imagined.
This means that
when you make some tight designs in Marvelous Designer,
you will think that
I have already made it very tight.
Why didn't it still have a fold effect?
Because our understanding is that
if a piece of clothing is very tight,
it will definitely have a fold effect.
But in fact,
sometimes if you use this board,
its stretch performance is better,
or the clothes are too tight,
it will not form a fold effect.
Because this board is strongly stretched,
it does not have the amount of fold effect here.
So, tightness does not mean that
the board must be reduced by five fingers.
Now let's take a look at
how to make a close-up,
but not too tight, board.
Before that,
I just mentioned that
our model has a surface diameter.
This surface diameter is the air thickness around the model.
Here we need to reduce the surface diameter to 1 or 0,
to make the air thickness around the model thinner,
so that the board is closer to the body.
Then I will choose to
give the sleeve a counter-activation first.
Because when you counter-activate the sleeve,
the sleeve will no longer have some pull on the big body.
Because if you simulate the sleeve and the big body at the same time,
when you adjust the shape of the board,
it is very difficult for you to control their fold direction together.
So I have already mentioned this method to you before.
Remember to counter-activate the sleeve first before adjusting it.
The air thickness I am talking about is
when you select a virtual model,
there is a thing called surface diameter in the model editor.
This surface diameter is the air thickness around the virtual model.
Where did we talk about just now?
Now I have counter-activated the sleeve,
everyone knows that when I counter-activate the sleeve,
the sleeve will no longer have any pull on the big body.
At this time, let's simulate the big body separately.
Take a look at the pressure diagram.
You will see that the bottom of the page is a dark area, right?
What is the difference between counter-activation and cold movement?
We have explained it many times in previous teaching videos.
If you have time,
you can take a look at the video of our technique sharing.
Most of the basic principle problems can be found in that video.
Since the bottom of the page is red,
we will modify the bottom of the page.
It is tight here,
so we will pull the bottom of the page down a little bit,
so that the bottom of the page is not too close to the bottom of the page.
After that, after we adjust it far away from the page,
it still has a red area, right?
That proves that it has nothing to do with the high and low points of the sleeve.
Instead, we need to widen its chest.
So here we will increase its chest a little bit,
which is to stretch the bottom of the page outwards.
Okay, now after we have adjusted it,
you will see that it no longer has those
very serious stretch and deformation parts.
After that, we will modify the waist.
Now you can see that its entire curve is not very smooth,
and it is not very good-looking.
In this case,
we will first pull the point of its waist out a little bit.
After that,
because what I am going to do now is a tight style,
you can open the transparent picture by pressing Alt 4.
After opening the transparent picture,
we will see that the curve on the side of this piece of clothing
is actually not in line with the curve of the human body.
So here we need to add two more straight lines
in the thinnest position of its waist.
Good evening, everyone.
After adding two more straight lines,
we go back to the previous mode,
which shows the pattern of the page.
After that,
we put these two points of the high waist position in.
After putting them in,
you can clearly see that the curve on the side
is in line with the human body.
So when you are changing this piece of clothing,
try to add more points
to control the direction of certain parts of the fold,
or certain parts of the page,
rather than adjusting the whole line.
Good.
After adjusting the waist here,
we can drag the page in 3D space
and pause it to take a look.
In fact, you can see that
the shape of our spine,
like the whole pressure chart now,
it is all blue and green.
It doesn't have that special,
very, very, very close situation.
Because our pressure line,
that is, the pressure chart,
its color is not yet reached the point
when the stretch and deformation are serious.
But at this time,
if you drag the page,
they can fold the fold out.
So the fold is often not in a particularly tight state,
but it is slightly stretched.
So when you are making clothes,
you must remember
not to make the clothes too tight.
After that,
we adjust the neck here.
Because the neck just now is a little high,
the position of the neck is a little high.
Let's adjust it again.
Good.
Then let's take a look at the shoulders.
Because the model we are using now,
its shoulders are relatively wide.
As for the wide position of this shoulder,
how do you look at it?
You can take a look at its chest.
This curve,
along this same slope,
extends upwards.
This is the actual position of the shoulder.
So you can compare the current clothes.
Take a look.
If you create a shirt according to the current position,
its shoulders will look particularly narrow,
particularly short.
The version I use is Marvelous Designer 11.
Okay.
So we need to modify its shoulder position later.
Of course,
if you click on the default model in our software,
you can also see its shoulder position.
The yellow highlight just now shows.
So we will extend the point of the shoulder to the end.
If you want to make it a little deeper,
then if you adjust the front,
you have to adjust the back at the same time.
After that,
when we were wearing our T-shirt just now,
its shoulder point extends outward.
Then the corresponding one,
because our sleeves and shoulders are connected,
so the point of the sleeves has to be dragged down.
So let them match.
After matching,
we will activate the sleeves again.
Activate the sleeves to simulate together.
Okay.
At this time,
after we started to simulate,
now in general,
in addition to the sleeves,
the stretch in other positions is not particularly serious.
The stretch of the sleeves here
is because we just stretched this point down and out.
Then this curve line
must be longer than the curve line of the sleeves part now.
Okay.
So now we are going to match the length of the sleeve curve line.
Of course,
you don't have to be very precise,
completely match.
But you just have to know that
these two values do not differ too much.
When you select the line section,
you can see in the attribute editor,
the total length of this line section.
Then we now match the line of this sleeve here.
Take a look.
For example, if it is 288,
we will try to make it match the sleeve curve line.
In this way,
the stretch will not be very serious.
After that,
let's take a look at this point.
Just now,
after we adjusted so many things to this sleeve,
the fake corner of the sleeve here
has become a sharp corner.
The sleeve is combined on both sides.
So there is a sharp corner here,
and another sharp corner here.
It can't form a flat corner.
When the two panels can't form a flat corner,
it is different from what it looks like.
When the two panels are combined,
the angle is not up to 360 degrees.
If the angle is not up to 360 degrees,
this point will form a sharp point,
rather than a flat surface.
Can you understand?
So this is why I remind you
when you usually go to match the panels,
sometimes you will feel that
some positions look very strange.
What is the reason?
The reason is that
when you match the panels,
you will feel that
some positions look very strange.
What is the reason?
The reason is that
sometimes you have to check
if they are combined into a flat surface.
If they are not combined into a flat surface.
If they are not combined into a flat surface,
or if these two corners,
you see,
now it is a sharp corner.
If the two corners are combined together,
and there is no 180 degree,
then it will be like this,
with the sharp corner protruding out,
or it will bend in.
It looks like the connection is not very smooth.
Then, like this,
we will use the editing curve tool
to adjust this curve,
so that its corner
will not be so sharp,
and then simulate it again.
At this time,
it will not be like
a point protruding out.
Then we will look at the sleeves.
Here,
we can clearly feel that
if you want to wrap your arm
after this dress,
then is it that
there is an extra part here?
Yes,
it is.
There is an extra part here.
You will think that
this arm is bent upwards.
In the case of a bent arm like this,
first of all,
we can use the sewing needle tool
to press the two sides
to sew this bent part together.
After sewing it together,
you will see that
if we put this point
and this point,
these two points,
like when we set it up with the computer,
will its curve be
closer to the arm than before?
That explains one thing,
that is,
there is an extra piece
in the middle of this plate.
Do you understand?
This method
has also been introduced to you
in the video of
making a sewing needle.
That is,
use a sewing needle
to make a rough reference
to see if there is an extra part
that needs to be cut off.
If there is,
use this sewing needle
to position it as a standard.
Then we cut off
the extra part.
Then we cut off the extra part.
So let's draw
an internal multidirectional line tool.
Draw here
two parts to be cut off.
Just two lines.
Then we cut off
the triangular area in the middle
and delete it.
After that,
combine the two sides
or sew them together.
You can take a look.
After we sew it up here,
you will see
that this curve
is not suitable for the arm.
So when we make some tight
but not too tight
clothing,
you can see that
the hard drawing is also very beautiful
and there is no stretch deformation
which is particularly serious.
So you can use this method
to determine the part
that needs to be cut off
with a sewing needle
and then cut them
and then combine them.
and then cut them and then combine them.
Because if you
directly adjust the plate,
sometimes
it is actually
a bit troublesome.
Or if you don't know
how to make a plate,
you can use this method
to avoid some problems.
Okay, then we combine
the two sides
now.
After that,
delete the extra points
in the middle.
Then we gradually
lengthen
this sleeve plate.
Because after we lengthen it,
we will see that
the sleeve here
is a bit longer.
So we will
shorten the sleeve here
a bit,
a bit narrower.
And then
I will
sew the sleeve
to,
for example,
the position of the arm.
Because what I originally thought
was to make it
a sleeve
that rolls up
is to roll up
to the position
of the elbow
near
it.
So I will
refer to
the position
of the elbow
first.
Pull this plate up
to see
its length.
For example,
if I put it
in this position now,
will its fold
be too much
or too little?
I don't set the friction.
You don't need to set
friction here
because
its sleeve
is tighter.
It can be
stuck
in the position
of your elbow.
Because
our muscle
direction is
that it will
change a lot first
and then
it will
shrink in
the elbow
and then
it will
be stuck
in the position
of the elbow.
You don't need to set
friction here.
OK.
Then I have
confirmed
that my
wrinkle distribution
is not too much.
This wrinkle
if I
put the sleeve
in the position
of the elbow
its wrinkle
will not be too much
or too little,
then
I will
reduce the
particle diameter
and confirm it again.
Because sometimes
when the particle diameter
is relatively large,
you can't see
the wrinkle.
If you can't see
the wrinkle,
you will feel that
its wrinkle
is about the same.
But when you
reduce the particle diameter,
because
the number of faces
increases
and there are some small
wrinkles,
you will feel that
there are still
some wrinkles.
So I will
continue to
modify the particle diameter
in the previous period
to see
and preview
its effect
and then
change the particle diameter
back.
OK.
Then
like this
and then
like the shoulder here,
I will use some force for it.
Just to see
when its shoulder
is stretched,
can its wrinkle
be stretched out?
If I
use some force
on its shoulder,
for example,
when I drag
this shoulder,
it can have
a wrinkle.
That means
its shape
is the effect
I want.
Why do I say this?
First of all,
if you can't form
a wrinkle here,
that is,
it can't have
that kind of
wrinkle,
because you need to know
how to form a wrinkle.
So
when you are doing
a competitive model,
sometimes
we will change
some movements
to make it
wrinkled.
Then
we will use,
for example,
a partial shape
to fix
these
wrinkled
because of
the change
in the movement.
So
when you drag
this plate,
you are imitating
those specific
movements.
When it
is stretched
by the shoulder,
this shape
is the effect
you want.
Then we can
make the following adjustments.
OK,
let's go back to
the time
when the sleeves
were not rolled up.
Because I have
been using
the default fabric
now,
plus I haven't made
the collar
in the front,
which is
the plate
with the button
button.
The name of the plate
with the button
is called
the collar.
Then
we can make
the collar.
OK,
after the
outer line
of the plate
is extended,
you have to remember
to choose
this line
before the
center line
and then
choose the
inner line
and then
the border
because we
sewed
the center line
before.
So
you have to make sure
that
the middle line
is still
in this position
after
the shoulder and
waist
will
change
because of
the increase
of the
collar.
So we have to control
that the middle line
is still in the middle
line.
So you have to
take this line
out and expand
it inside
and then
cut the
middle
plate
down
so that
its middle
line is still
in the middle
line.
Then
we
will
sew
some lines
here
so that
it can match
when sewing.
OK.
Okay.
Uh,
uh,
when
we finish
the middle line,
just
go hence
this side
Let's take a look at the shape of it, it is not stretched and deformed.
After that, we can add a button and a buttonhole.
This live broadcast is about three hours.
If it's fast, it's only three and a half hours if it's slow.
Then we add a buttonhole.
After you create a buttonhole,
we can use the editor to select the move buttonhole tool.
Select the buttonhole or buttonhole, Ctrl C, Ctrl V.
Press the Shift key to create in the horizontal or vertical direction.
Then press the right key to enter the specific value,
that is, how many duplicates are pasted.
Through this method, you can let the buttonhole create multiple with a specific value.
Create multiple buttons at the same time.
Buttonhole or buttonhole.
That is, create one first and then duplicate it.
During the process of duplicating, press the right mouse button.
You can create N buttons at the same time.
Buttonhole or buttonhole.
Now we have created a buttonhole on the symmetrical version.
What we are going to do next is to select these buttonholes and right-click.
Duplicate the buttonhole to the symmetrical version.
After duplicating, we will use the move buttonhole tool to remember the buttonhole and buttonhole.
That's it.
At this time, if you look closely at the side of the buttonhole,
you can see that there is a wave line.
This wave line means that the buttonhole has started to stretch.
Let's reduce the overall particle diameter and the conflict thickness.
Here I will reduce the particle diameter to 15.
I won't reduce it to 5 or 10 during the simulation process.
After that, we can slowly reduce it.
As for the physical properties of the fabric,
because now we have to control these folds through the physical properties of the fabric.
So here we first find a suitable physical property of the fabric.
Considering that many people wear wool clothes,
I chose linen here, which is the material of the wool.
This physical property is preset.
After selecting this preset, you can feel it clearly.
Since the buttonhole itself has a relatively high particle diameter,
it is not easy to stretch.
It is more likely to form creases.
Because creases are all creases generated by the strength of the stretch.
So the worse your stretch,
for example, the higher the particle diameter of the buttonhole,
the easier it is to produce these creases.
After we change the buttonhole fabric,
you can see that there will be some creases on this clothes.
The chest has some creases here,
we can solve this problem later with a sewing needle.
Then we take a look at
pulling the sleeve up.
This is the reason why the sleeve is stocked like this,
on the top it is stacked, and the bottom is flat.
Because I need to fold the flat section afterwards,
and this way I get the effect of turning the sleeve.
So I can guarantee that it is foldable above the elbow.
It's a fold, and below the fold is a flat stitch.
Okay, after I just pulled it up, I felt that the sleeve is still a little big.
It can't be fixed in this position very well.
Then I will shrink the sleeve a little bit.
In fact, you can see that although we adjusted the version before,
its shape is relatively close.
Here we use a false stitch to fix it.
Although the whole version is relatively close,
but as long as you change a fabric that is not easy to stretch,
it can still form a fold.
So let's do it again.
Don't do it too tight when you usually make clothes.
Take a closer look at the hard drawing.
Okay, then add the collar.
I don't know if you usually do a shirt,
do you feel that the collar version is a bit difficult to draw?
Because you can't make sure that the collar is like a shirt,
the collar is separated.
Sometimes the collar is difficult to draw.
If you click on the title of the window on the left,
there is a called Modular Configurator in the drop-down menu.
This is actually our
modular controller in Marvelous Designer.
In the modular controller,
you can switch different modules,
or switch different modules,
and you can import different parts of the clothing.
So here we can also extract the existing material.
We actually have mentioned this in many live broadcasts.
I won't introduce this in detail.
For example, here I can double-click to import a collar.
If I think the collar is difficult to draw,
I will import the existing collar.
Then we will open the middle line of the collar along the middle line.
Because the collar in the modular configurator
is not symmetrical on the left and right.
In short, the collar here,
we cut it in half first,
and then click on Control D to create a symmetrical collar.
After creating a symmetrical collar,
now our collar is symmetrical on the left and right.
In the 3D space,
arrange the collar first.
Then here we delete the extra buttons and buttons.
Notice that the position of the buttons and buttons
must be in line with the body.
Then we can sew this panel and the collar together.
In the process of sewing,
remember to press the Shift key
to sew a whole section and multiple sections.
We first select the first section,
which is the first section of a whole section.
Then press the Shift key,
click,
and then select the multiple sections and sections
that are sewn with it.
This is the one-to-multi-sew.
Press the Shift key.
After sewing,
release the Shift key.
Then we sew the front middle and the back middle together.
Not the front middle and the back middle,
but the two back middles together.
After sewing,
our collar is sewn here.
let's compare again.
The length of the collar here is relatively short,
so let's stretch the collar here again.
Okay.
Then press the Shift key to edit the sewing line.
You can compare the length of the sewing line.
If the length of the sewing line is different,
that is, it jumps out and is a red color,
that means that the length difference between them is relatively large.
Just remind you,
unless you do something specific,
such as the wrinkle on the edge of the flower,
or the wrinkle on the edge of the collar,
you certainly don't want it to have a lot of wrinkles.
Because the length of the collar here,
if the length of the collar here is different,
it will pull,
that is, it will pull some wrinkles along the collar,
which is not very good.
After that,
we apply the same fabric to the collar here.
Because I want its chest to be open later,
so we don't need to use a particularly hard fabric for the collar here.
As long as it looks loose and loose,
that's fine.
Then we can choose,
to sew the buttons,
and then click on the button that has been sewn,
we can untie them.
Then manually pull the panel,
so that it becomes,
that is, the collar is open,
not buttoned up.
Hello, hello, good evening everyone.
Next, I will teach you another method.
Let me take a look.
Hard collar fabric,
use fusible rigid,
that fabric,
that fabric is not easy to stretch.
But you have to pay attention,
for a plate like a shirt,
usually only the collar will use this fabric.
If you also use this fabric for the collar,
because it is hard,
its folding effect may look relatively hard.
You need to pay attention,
or it will be easy,
because if this plate is a harder plate,
then,
the length will be different from other plates.
For example,
the length of the plate that it is folded,
if its length is not the same,
it may be because of the stretch,
because it is not easy to stretch.
The plate that it is folded may be deformed.
Do you understand?
So you have to pay attention.
If this is the case,
it is appropriate to reduce the strength of the collar,
and the tension of the collar line.
Okay.
Then here,
I will teach you a little trick.
That is to say,
if you want,
for example,
like we will test here,
if we pull this position,
when this point is stretched outward,
are there any wrinkles on the shoulder here?
Right?
That means,
if this point,
it,
wait a minute,
this point,
its actual position should be in the center,
in the center here,
then,
the shoulder here will naturally produce wrinkles.
So we have to put this point in the front,
and move this line in front of it.
It is equivalent to narrowing its front chest,
the width of the front chest,
the width of the entire front piece.
Just now,
this point,
now,
is it sewed together?
Right?
We can imagine it,
and put it on.
In this way,
do you see?
The wrinkles here will become obvious.
So,
in fact,
when you take off the plate,
there is also a skill.
You have to remember,
I almost,
this chest,
where to shrink a little,
or the waist,
to shrink a little,
will it make the wrinkles here more obvious?
If so,
you have to modify the plate.
In addition,
there is another way,
that is,
you can make some wrinkles here on the chest.
By the way,
that's why,
here,
these wrinkles can occur,
and it won't fall down.
It's because,
these wrinkles,
it's because our plate,
its vertical direction is relatively long.
But,
did you see,
the bottom plate here is very flat,
there are no wrinkles.
It's because,
this piece,
it's relatively tight.
So,
the bottom plate of the plate,
is fixed in this position.
Then,
the middle part,
will naturally,
stack up,
and form a wrinkle.
So,
you can manually take off the plate,
and then,
the bottom part,
put it in,
and then,
the wrinkle will be fixed in this position.
OK.
Then,
let's reduce the particle diameter a little bit.
OK.
Then,
let's take a look again.
If we move this point down again,
this wrinkle will be more obvious.
So, sometimes,
my wrinkle,
it may not be completely aligned.
I may choose,
to slightly move the position of the wrinkle a little bit.
So,
when we align the wrinkle again,
there will be a new wrinkle.
So,
when we make clothes in real life,
we will say,
oh,
this dress needs to be,
well,
symmetrical to look good.
But,
in fact,
when we use software,
you don't have to be completely symmetrical.
For example,
now,
I deliberately move the wrinkle a little bit.
These two wrinkle are closer,
but their wrinkle is also far away.
Then,
through some small modifications like this,
it can also produce some stretching wrinkles.
If it is more serious,
or more deformed,
we will return it to its original position a little bit.
Through the wrong position of the wrinkle,
in fact,
sometimes,
it can also form a lot of wrinkles we want.
So,
you can try it.
If you want to do this,
it looks more casual,
or more casual,
some wrinkles,
it will separate the wrinkle.
Well,
yes,
when the wrinkle is pulled out,
or the zipper is usually pulled out together with the clothes.
The zipper,
if you want to pull it out alone,
it is also possible.
Well,
there are two problems with the wrinkle and the zipper.
Because of the zipper,
you can't pull it out through the unified map.
If you want to pull out the zipper,
because the zipper does not have a UV map,
so when you pull out the zipper,
you have to pull out the zipper alone.
But the wrinkle is together with the clothes,
because the wrinkle has a UV map.
Well,
where are we talking about?
Oh,
we are talking about the button.
Yes,
I will deliberately open the button to adjust it.
Then,
here,
the zipper,
I think the position of the zipper is a little too close.
So,
I will delete the zipper again.
Well,
now I think its wrinkle is almost done.
When I think it looks more cautious,
I will do this sleeve part.
Well,
since we are going to do the sleeve,
we don't need the button,
so let's freeze the button first.
Well,
let me take off the sleeve first.
Pull the pleats of the upper part of the sleeve here.
Then we are going to fold the sleeve.
So the order of folding the sleeve is not like this in our real life.
Fold the sleeve first,
just a little bit,
and then turn it over directly.
Instead,
first,
fix the pleats of the upper part of the sleeve here,
and then adjust this panel separately.
Just imagine this panel as two parts.
One part is the part with the pleats,
and the other part is the flat one.
Later,
we are going to turn over the sleeve part.
Transparency,
Transparency is Alt 4.
Alt 4 is to open the transparency map,
or you can open the transparency map here.
Well,
we will draw here first.
And then we have to fold the fold line.
After folding,
use the fold arrangement tool to fold the top line first.
This is not the same as folding the sleeve in our real life.
In real life,
when you fold the sleeve,
you first turn the first circle,
turn this side up,
and then press this side,
and then turn this side in,
right?
But in software,
it is not possible.
Because when you use the fold arrangement tool,
the whole,
that is,
this line,
all the panels on one side will be folded over.
So we fold the top line first.
Do you understand?
Okay,
after folding,
simulate it.
It must be unstable.
Because the sleeves are closer to the bottom,
the narrower,
the tighter.
So we have to make sure it is simulated and stable.
But if you are here,
because the bottom part of this line is already tight,
and then this is already turned over,
if you are along the middle line,
because it is now wrapped around your arm,
under the situation of wrapping around your arm,
we are already close to the human body,
you are in the middle of these two panels,
to clip a panel,
and it is using the fold arrangement,
it is the form of a fold over the entire grid,
then it will definitely be worn out,
it will definitely be unstable.
Even if it is not unstable,
the effect of it is not particularly good.
So here,
we have to change the method to solve this problem.
First of all,
first of all,
untie the sewing,
put this extra panel,
this part,
that is,
we don't care about the upper part of these forms,
it is already in the position we want,
just separate it and think about it,
freeze it.
Let's do this fold position separately.
I just told you that
because now you turn it over,
the position of the arm,
it is wrapped around the human body,
it is too tight,
there is no way to clip a layer in the middle,
so now we turn it over first,
there is a space to turn the panel in,
then here,
we are going to use the shrink,
to temporarily shrink it,
that is,
widen it a little bit.
The shrink has an end-to-end effect,
how to divide this end-to-end effect,
just go to the previous video,
use the editing logic tool to select the panel,
and then you can see the direction.
Okay,
after we add an end-to-end effect to it,
let's print the panel,
after printing the panel,
we can fold this panel,
but you imagine,
because now,
this panel,
it looks like it has been widened,
after widening,
because it looks like it has been widened,
so it has some,
that is,
it can't maintain its original width,
if you turn it over again,
this panel will still come out,
then here,
we change another way to do it,
this is my own research method,
that is,
here,
we cut it a little bit,
and then select this one,
it should be turned over to the inside,
this layer of panel,
and then right-click,
there is an addition to the outside,
note that this is also added to the outside,
because this panel is facing the back,
so although it is in our mind,
turn it inside,
but in fact,
it is in the 3D space,
it should belong to this,
the outside of this panel,
because you are going to put this panel,
stick to the outside of this panel,
because it is facing the back,
so we choose to add it to the outside,
of course,
if you can't distinguish it,
it is added to the outside,
or added to the inside,
you can just choose one,
just choose one,
and then look at its position,
right?
For example,
here,
I choose to add it to the outside,
because it is added to the outside,
it will stick to the panel,
just stick it in,
so we can guarantee,
although the panel outside is crooked,
but the panel attached to it,
can also be placed along this crooked position,
and then we simulate it again,
it is stable,
see?
So using this method to turn the sleeve,
relatively speaking,
it can guarantee that you will turn it out,
it must be more beautiful,
and more stable,
because we usually turn the sleeves,
the most common problem is not stable,
it must be stable,
right?
Okay,
then we put this inside,
turn to the inside,
the shrinkage of the panel,
put it back,
put it back to 100,
and then the shrinkage of the panel on the outside,
we first reduce it to 130,
because the sleeves are tight now,
if you give this panel too much pressure,
if you pull it too tight,
it may be a little unstable,
our shrinkage here is a little bit lower,
okay,
then the sleeves,
usually after I turn the sleeves on one side,
I will delete the other side,
and then control again,
create a symmetrical panel,
so that my sleeves don't have to be turned twice,
I can just use the linear symmetry to match it.
Okay,
then simulate it again,
then about this issue of turning the sleeves,
if you think it is still not understood in the live broadcast,
if it is particularly transparent,
in the video of skill sharing,
there is a lesson of turning the sleeves,
you can go and learn,
okay,
then just now we mentioned that
the corner of the two sides of this panel is best to be a straight corner,
it sounds a little sleepy,
do you need to put some bgm?
Put the two sides together,
sew and then simulate it,
do you need me to put some bgm?
Wait a minute,
let me find some bgm for you,
so we'll do it from the other side,
now I'll show you what you will do,
then you can say,
okay,
you can turn this way,
you can say,
sorry,
I'll just put the two sides together,
it will be exactly the same,
I will put the two sides together,
Hello? Hello? Hello?
If I play other songs, my thoughts will be taken over, so I can only play a little bit of fast songs.
Okay, very energetic. Okay, okay.
Okay, so where are we talking about?
Then put this sleeve in place. After that, I may be able to drag its position manually.
Then our sleeve will be turned over.
Then the outer layer is turned over to the outside of this plate.
Don't change its shrinkage.
Because if you change its shrinkage, it may be a little unstable.
For example, I'll show you here.
If you put this in the middle, that is, we are looking at the outside of this plate.
If you change its shrinkage, how will it be?
For example, change to 100.
Oh, you simulate it and it starts to be unstable.
It's very shaky, right?
Then in such a situation,
Then you just don't change its shrinkage.
Or don't change it so small.
Ah, we can't play Jay Chou's songs when we are live streaming.
Because we are an official channel, we can't play these songs.
When I'm doing the file myself, I also play Jay Chou's songs.
I have a song list full of Jay Chou's songs.
Then activate the version.
Increase its particle diameter a little bit.
Because we are at the last step.
The last step.
In order to ensure the smoothness of the previous period.
Because the whole file will finally make a very, very large number of copies in it.
If you finish a part, you will first lower its particle diameter very low.
Then this file will definitely be stuck in the back.
That is, no matter how good your computer is, it will be stuck.
So in the middle, I will return its particle diameter.
Then ensure that its overall simulation is stable.
We are the frozen version.
This can save some computing.
In this case, I set the width of the final version, i.e. the horizontal width of the finished version, to 80 percent.
So that it will shrink to a tight dress.
This is for our convenience.
Wait a minute, wear pants outside.